let questions = [
  {
    question:
      "WhatsApp concurrent model is implemented using _____ programming language.",
    answers: {
      optOne: "Java",
      optTwo: "Node.js",
      optThree: "Erlang",
      optFour: "C",
    },
    correctAnswer: "Erlang",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is not a type of computer code related to Program Execution?",
    answers: {
      optOne: "Source code",
      optTwo: "Hex Code",
      optThree: "Machine Code",
      optFour: "Bytecode",
    },
    correctAnswer: "Hex Code",
  },
  {
    question: "The following are programming languages except?",
    answers: {
      optOne: "Javascript",
      optTwo: "python",
      optThree: "C++",
      optFour: "CSS",
    },
    correctAnswer: "CSS",
  },
  {
    question: "One of the following is not a javascript library",
    answers: {
      optOne: "ReactJs",
      optTwo: "Angular",
      optThree: "Vue",
      optFour: "Django",
    },
    correctAnswer: "Django",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following includes Chromes V8 JavaScript Engine?",
    answers: {
      optOne: "Nodejs",
      optTwo: "jQuery",
      optThree: "npm",
      optFour: "Java",
    },
    correctAnswer: "Nodejs",
  },
  {
    question: "The binary equivalent of 50 is",
    answers: {
      optOne: "1010110",
      optTwo: "1100110",
      optThree: "110010",
      optFour: "110101",
    },
    correctAnswer: "110010",
  },
  {
    question: "The following are tech opportunities except",
    answers: {
      optOne: "Software Engineer",
      optTwo: "Full stack Engineer",
      optThree: "Backend Engineer",
      optFour: "Content Creator",
    },
    correctAnswer: "Content Creator",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What does JavaScript return to you if you try to access a object property that does not exist?",
    answers: {
      optOne: "null",
      optTwo: "undefined",
      optThree: "0",
      optFour: "Object not found",
    },
    correctAnswer: "undefined",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which type of language is translated entirely to machine language before use?",
    answers: {
      optOne: "Assembly",
      optTwo: "Interpreted",
      optThree: "Machine",
      optFour: "Compiled",
    },
    correctAnswer: "Compiled",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which type of error occurs when a programmer misspells a word or instruction?",
    answers: {
      optOne: "Runtime",
      optTwo: "Syntax",
      optThree: "System",
      optFour: "Semantic",
    },
    correctAnswer: "Syntax",
  },
];
